[MUSIC]
[MÚSICA]
Emily and I really hope you've enjoyed the course so far.
Emily y yo esperamos que estén disfrutando el curso hasta ahora
We've really explored the foundations of machine learning on a wide range of
Hemos explorado los fundamentos del aprendizaje automático en una amplia gama de
domains with a range of different applications.
dominios con una amplia gama de aplicaciones
And really touched many of the practical issues around deploying and
Y henos tocado muchas cuestiones en torno a la aplicación y
building machine learning systems.
desarrollo de sistemas de aprendizaje automático
And now in this closing module we're going to really summarize some of the concepts
Y ahora en éste módulo de cierre resumiremos algunos conceptos
that we've learned.
que hemos aprendido
Talk about how to deploy these ideas,
de cómo implementar éstas ideas
especially machine learning systems in production and
especialmente los sistemas de aprendizaje automático en producción y
then what's ahead in the specialization and in machine learning as a whole.
y lo que viene en la especialización de aprendizaje automático
Some really exciting stuff as we close off this first course.
Algunas cosas son realmente emocionantes
[MUSIC]
[MÚSICA]